<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
	<title>LibertyImp</title>
	<link>http://libertyimp.xyz/</link>
	<description>Recent content on LibertyImp</description>
	<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
	<language>en-us</language>
    
        <atom:link href="http://libertyimp.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


	
	<item>
		<title>Cryptocurreny Is Currency</title>
		<link>http://libertyimp.xyz/cryptocurreny-is-currency/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 17:52:34 -0500</pubDate>
		
		<guid>http://libertyimp.xyz/cryptocurreny-is-currency/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s start this blog off with a bit of a diss towards the brainlets who use crypto as a glorified stock market/slot machine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;brainlet-mentality&#34;&gt;Brainlet mentality&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HEY MOM! guess what? My i gaineded 40USD becuz I hab moniez in da bitcoin and da numer go upptie and make me big rich rich durrrrr&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you can see I absolutly despise these kinds of people, It&amp;rsquo;s one thing to exchange fiat for crypto and stake it to support a network (though I will always support PoW over PoS) but for most of these numb skulls they don&amp;rsquo;t even remotly care about the technology they are abusing they simply think, &amp;ldquo;I can make more fiat&amp;rdquo; that it, the whole goal is more fiat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This completly defeats the purpose of a cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;big-brain-mentality&#34;&gt;Big brain mentality&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The value of my cryptocurrency has gone up, I will spend it now to get more out of what I&amp;rsquo;m already holding. It is pretty nice when the number goes up but at the end of the day one (crypto token of your choosing) is equal to one (crypro token of your choosing).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spending and Saving at the sametime like you would with fiat is the true use case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading :)
If i made you made&amp;hellip; well&amp;hellip; STAY MAD! &amp;gt;:)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>New Site</title>
		<link>http://libertyimp.xyz/new-site/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 16:00:48 -0500</pubDate>
		
		<guid>http://libertyimp.xyz/new-site/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t noticed I have completly switched up the look on my website for what I think is the better(hopefully you agree lol) I will do my best to keep things mostly up to date and will keep the blogs rolling again, its been awhile since i have made a blog post and so i hope to get back into it again. I will be speaking on things of intrest such as games, computer stuff, politics, general thoughts/opinions and other stuff as well so keep an eye out :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;** Thanks for reading :)**&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>
